I'm on a journey out to see
the world While I'm on my own,
I've yet to reach the end So won't
you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea
For that treasure known
by everybody as One Piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm.
The storm that you have built within.
Manhattan, our board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up.
We set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall.
And take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to sea.
The world done on.
On my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
Is that a prehistoric mammoth?
I see.
The enemies wanted what you didn't have.
There was nothing you
could do, you understand?
Rizal, huh? From Wanhole?
We've never heard of him!
Yeah, we can't help!
Alright, go away!
You're all minx here.
Legends really are true.
A whole country of you talking fleabags.
Shut up!
And just who are you, Karoo?
Really?
Oh, who are we?
Take a look, stupid!
You've never heard of this man?
Our leader is one of the three disasters,
which means he's a top member
of Emperor Kaido's crew.
He's feared far and wide
as Jack the Drought.
And how did he earn
that title, you may ask?
Every nation he passes
through is left so barren,
it looks like they suffered a drought.
Now we wouldn't want your country
to meet such a cruel fight.
So hand over Race, or your children
won't have a future anymore.
What's that?
You want to fight Jack? Huh?
Yeah!
A fight's the last thing we want.
Margie!
Please, stay calm.
If you, Karoo, would only listen
to us, we could make peace.
The man you want cannot be found on Zo.
Master Jack, I promise,
we minks do not tell lies.
If you, Karoo, want to search for Race,
you're free to go door to door all day.
Women, children, who cares?
Kill them all!
Jinrumi, we are not here to talk. Are we?
No, sir, Master Jack.
We're here for Raizo,
the samurai from Wano.
Moron!
He's not a samurai.
Raizo is a ninja. Come on!
You think I don't know that?
Samurai is a general term.
They use it all the time. Uh-uh!
A ninja is a ninja!
Bring Raizo to me or face destruction!
There is no negotiation!
So it was Kaido's crew that attacked.
And they're the Beast Pirates?
That's right.
We're not lying! Really!
We don't know any rhizo!
What else can we say?
Find gold pleasures!
Search every last inch!
My boy!
Kill him!
That'll show him what we're made of!
No mercy!
What are you idiots doing?
That power is just pathetic.
We're peaceful, but that
doesn't mean we're weak.
Every mink has a gift.
From our birth, we're given this strength.
Even a child won't be bested easily.
You, Karoo, may be strong,
but do you think you can fight
every single person in this country?
We have highly trained musketeers as well;
their power is far beyond
anything seen here.
If we fight, then both of us
will suffer needless casualties.
If you, Karoo, are intent
on finding this, Rhizo,
then why not meet with the Duke
of our country and talk it out?
Talk it out!
I refuse.
Gifters, you're up.
Yes, sir.
Oh, geez.
That's not natural.
Go!
Find that ninja!
Destroy everything in your path!
They wouldn't listen to a word we said.
Even though they had nothing to gain,
they turned Kuro City into a battlefield.
We were forced to either fight or die.
There were countless injuries,
so those who could walk had
to carry those who could not.
It was a terrible sight.
We also don't know how he managed
to make his way to our country,
or why he was so certain that Raizo
was here despite our protests.
Usa, bet that mammoth was huge, huh?
Shh, get excited later.
Raid out Rome! Huh?
You see?
Watch what you say to the Minx.
So no, ninja, samurai,
or land of Wano talk.
Fair enough.
What awful people.
If they find out that Kin'emon has a
possible connection to this tragedy,
it could be a complete disaster.
What a bummer.
Hmm.
Uh-uh.
Where's that ninja from Wano?
Kin'emon wanted to see him, right?
What a shame.
Ah!
Ninja?
Hmm?
Huh? Bulldog!
I see.
So you are familiar with that, Drum.
Then Yutia must know something about Wano.
Yeah, I think you simply misheard him.
What he actually said was, uh...
Injured!
He's worried about your injured dog!
I don't think I like Mink's ship anymore.
So, uh, we'll be there soon, right?
Yes, I can see the
sanatorium straight ahead.
Thank you, Tia, for coming along.
I can finish the story another time.
Please forgive us!
We didn't mean to!
Mercy, show mercy!
Sir Cecilion's on a rampage!
That sounds bad.
Sir Cecilion, what's the matter?
Oh, hello, Wanda.
Those fools kept spewing
some sugary nonsense.
So I taught them a lesson and
tossed them straight off a ledge.
Cupcakes, match, love,
babies, sugar, and honey!
Never speak these sickeningly
sweet words in my presence,
or I'll tear your windpipes out!
Now, pull it together and climb back up!
Oh, that's true kindness.
What did you gotta say?
Mere seconds after my scathing
rebuke, you fools get sappy again!
How dare you gotta!
That hurt, but he's so cool.
We're sorry.
We'll never say anything sweet again.
Say that you gotta don't.
Sir Sashillian.
What now?
These people here are
the Straw Hat Pirates.
You gotta have my boundless
gratitude for saving this country.
It's a lifelong death
that I can never repay.
Sir Shishilian always puts his
full power into everything he does.
Maybe you should hold back a little.
You gotta may see the Duke.
Come inside. Don't delay.
Hey, they're here!
Oh my grace, I'm so glad you're well.
So you Karoo are the Straw Hats.
I owe you Karoo for the
lives of everyone on Zo.
Words cannot express my things.
I heard my crew saved
you, but I just got here.
So I still don't know the whole story yet.
Even if you Karoo weren't all
here, the whole crew played a part.
Anyway, I bet you're strong.
Like, really strong.
Of course! Don't be rude.
Our duke is the mightiest
warrior in the whole country.
And yet I lost.
Praising my strength now as cruel.
That was not your fault.
The Beast Pirates were mighty indeed, but
Yutia still maintained the upper hand.
It was...
A poison gas.
No way!
Know what that means?
The gas used on this place was
one of Caesar's weapons And I see
the connection now Kaido's bio-weapons
came straight from Doflamingo
Caesar!
What do we have here?
Oh, please, no!
You must be admiring our
savior, Baron Corpse.
What a delectable-looking hero.
I know he's tempting,
but you're still injured.
Maybe later.
How about you don't?
I'm already!
I couldn't help but notice that hat
it suits you Karoo very well pirate
takes me back to my youth ah traveling
with damn it what's that cat's
name it's master cat viper sir I
was sailing the seas with that fool
many years ago there was a young
man with a hat just like yours he's
an emperor now his name was shanks
you used to sail with shakes really
actually this hat belongs
to him and hey rude
it is already six o
'clock what is he a baby
wake up boss dog as i mentioned
before the mokumo duktim is
governed by two rulers though they
never ruled during the same time.
Duke Dogstorm is the official
sovereign of this nation.
The Master Cat Viper, who guards the Sacred
Whale Forest, possesses equal authority,
at least when the night falls.
That's interesting and all, but what does
it have to do with a Duke falling asleep?
I see a happy move!
To say they hate each other
would be an understatement.
If they met face to face, it's possible
that they would fight to the death.
Fight to the death? What?
They were once friends,
but whatever happened between
them, they don't talk about it.
Well, at any rate,
the two of them possess equal power, both
as kings and as mighty make warriors.
They ended up fighting so often that they
decided to never see each other again.
So one rules under the sun, from six
in the morning to six in the evening.
And the other rules under the moon, from
six in the evening to six in the morning.
Thus divided, the two kings ensure
that they never cross paths.
I wonder how it got that bad between them.
Ah!
Even his doctors go to sleep too?
It's not only his doctors,
but everyone in the fortress.
I'm starting to nod off.
Hey, that lion bro is...
It's Cecilion!
Always at full power!
Okay, you don't have to yell at me!
The country follows a day and night
cycle, just like the two kings.
So those who live in the city are
active during the daylight hours.
and those who live in the forest
are not terrible like me.
Keep searching.
I know Race is hiding somewhere.
Stop it!
Haven't you thug done
enough damage already?
This is getting bad.
Where's the samurai, doggie? Not here.
I promise you...
Too bad.
You're useless.
Here come the musketeers!
Huh? All right!
Everyone else step back!
They're gonna handle this!
Focus on disarming the enemy!
Our goal is to minimize the damage! Sir!
Carrot, are you ready?
Uh-huh!
What are these people?
They're creepy.
Some have disturbing powers.
A race that we don't know?
I fear they are something unnatural.
Watch out for the ones with blackhorns!
Try my wolf grip!
What did he do?
Now die!
Wonder be countered!
You gotta step back!
They're in trouble now!
Woohoo!
The three musketeers!
All of the musketeers, lead the
citizens to the forest immediately! Sir!
More insects to squash.
So you Karoo Jack, stop all of this
violence and destruction at once.
You must be the ruler.
I'm confused, sir.
Why drop your blade?
I shall not take up arms.
This samurai is not here.
You, Karoo, are free to search
and find out for yourself.
But let it be done peacefully.
I won't see our heritage destroyed.
I refuse!
Don't just stand there for the way!
Oh no, the poor Duke!
hold up what's with that dog guy he
stood there and didn't even flinch
that's our duke stout-hearted
and true i didn't realize they
had a guy this strong I thought this place
was full of fuzzy, woodland creatures!
Don't make me laugh!
You really think you're that tough, huh?
You're up against Master Jack here!
He's feared by all!
Surely you know the bounty on his head
alone is worth one billion berries?
So just because you're a little strong
don't think you can push your lock,
that's enough.
Blabbing about me, believe me:
we speak the truth;
we are not concealing the samurai.
I'm gonna make this clear.
Your greatest sin is protecting
Rhizo—if you can't find him,
it's your own fault.
He's an insane monster.
And
one more thing.
I revel in destruction.
This
is a disaster!
disaster
Onward!
Oh, that rain it was.
Goloniago!
Yaaah!
That sounded like master cat viper's roar.
The fool of the night has come to
play, then it's time to retreat.
Shouldn't we fight with them?
Fall back; switching off
will be to our benefit.
The enemy will weaken after
not being able to rest.
Oh, I get it, jack;
do not believe that you Karoo
are the only stubborn one here.
Here, for every nation
has its share of fools.
Bolognago!
When the moon goes up, this is my turn!
No intruder will escape on my watch!
Entering my home while I sleep!
He sleeps, Monster Kitty!
Master Jack!
We have so much to tell you, Grove!
Yeah, yeah, I already
heard the whole story.
So, if I got this straight, you're
looking for a water warrior.
I wouldn't let a samurai step
a damn foot on this island.
And if one even dared, I would chew
through every limb on his body.
I'm the fearless cat viper, the man
who waits for the god of the world.
Master Charge!
Thank you.